<doc>
   <page width="210" height="297">
      <pdf id="Back1" title="Page 1 - Background Silhouette" lowerleftx="11" lowerlefty="11" upperrightx="198" upperrighty="285" editable="false" />
      <text-block-group id="Group1" title="" lowerleftx="11" lowerlefty="11" upperrightx="198" upperrighty="130" editable="true" align="left" verticalalign="top" spacing="18">
         <text-block id="EventName" title="Page 1 - Event name" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" textmode="multiline" font-size="36" editable="true" maxlen="55">Event name/description which can go across two lines</text-block>
         <text-block id="EventDescription" title="Page 1 - Event description" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" textmode="multiline" font-size="20" editable="true" maxlen="600">This double-sided flyer is designed for events which need a longer description. The maximum is 600 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 10 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs. Putting in more lines of text than this will make the text too small to be read easily. Fewer lines of text mean that the text will be larger. This double-sided flyer is designed for events which need a longer description. The maximum is 600 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 10 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs.</text-block>
      </text-block-group>
   </page>
   <page width="210" height="297">
      <text-block-group id="Group2" title="" lowerleftx="11" lowerlefty="60" upperrightx="149" upperrighty="285" editable="true" align="left" verticalalign="top" spacing="18">
         <text-block id="EventNameDescription" title="Page 2 - Event name" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" font-size="36" textmode="multiline" editable="true" maxlen="30">Event name/description</text-block>
         <text-block id="EventDescription2" title="Page 2 - Event description" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" textmode="multiline" font-size="20" editable="true" maxlen="900">This double-sided flyer is designed for events which need a longer description. The maximum is 900 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 20 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs. Putting in more lines of text than this will make the text too small to be read easily. Fewer lines of text mean that the text will be larger. This double-sided flyer is designed for events which need a longer description. The maximum is 900 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 20 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs. Putting in more lines of text than this will make the text too small to be read easily. Fewer lines of text mean that the text will be larger. This double-sided flyer is designed for events which need a longer description. The maximum is 900 characters in this section.</text-block>
         <text-block id="AdditionalText" title="Page 2 - Additional Text" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" font-size="14" textmode="multiline" editable="true" maxlen="900">The maximum is 900 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 14 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs. Putting in more lines of text than this will make the text too small to be read easily. Fewer lines of text mean that the text will be larger. The rest of this text is holding text, so that you can get an idea of what your resource will look like. Time, date and location of event. Contact tel 01234 567 890 or email anyone@myorg.org.uk The maximum is 900 characters in this section, but this should not be more than 14 lines of text – including the line spaces between paragraphs. Putting in more lines of text than this will make the text too small to be read easily. Fewer lines of text mean that the text will be larger. The rest of this text is holding text, so that you can get an idea of what your resource will look like.</text-block>
      </text-block-group>
      <text-block id="FooterText" title="Footer text" font-family="FuturaBT-Heavy" font-size="8" editable="false" align="left" lowerleftx="11" lowerlefty="11" upperrightx="198" upperrighty="15">Organised in aid of Macmillan Cancer Support, registered charity in England and Wales (261017), Scotland (SC039907) and the Isle of Man (604). Also operating in Northern Ireland.</text-block>
      <image id="EditableLogoH" title="Page 2 - Horizontal Brand Logo" lowerleftx="12" lowerlefty="20" upperrightx="198" upperrighty="54" editable="true" verticalalign="bottom" />
      <image id="EditableLogoV" title="Page 2 - Vertical Brand Logo" lowerleftx="156" lowerlefty="60" upperrightx="198" upperrighty="285" editable="true" align="right" verticalalign="top" />
   </page>
</doc>